Zack, Arnold Additional Arbitration Files 5659
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files
1978-1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zack, Arnold
5659
8 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Arbitration decisions, records.
5685211
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 07, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 04, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Lawyer, arbitrator, and government official; LLB Yale, 1956, MBA Harvard, 1961, MA Harvard, 1963.
Arnold Marshall Zack is an arbitrator and mediator. Beginning his labor career as a part-time election examiner for the National Labor Relations Board and as a case analyst for the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board (1950-1953), he was also a lecturer in labor economics at Simmons College, Northeastern University (1957-1963); an assistant to Saul Wallen, arbitrator, (1956-1960); director of the Labor-Management Institute of the American Academy of Arbitrators (1966-1968); and has served in various labor-related international posts for the United States government.
Other governmental service includes membership on panels for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, the Massachusetts Public Employment Relations Board, the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, The New Jersey Public Employment Relations Board, The New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, and The National Mediation Board. Zack is also a panel member of the American Arbitration Association, and has served as the permanent arbitrator for a number of major corporations and unions and for the State of New York and the U.S. Postal Service.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5281: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5515: Maurice F. Neufeld Collection of New York Times Clippings 5551: Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5620: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5727: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial.; Zack, Arnold.
5685211
- Acme Markets - Commonwealth of Massachusetts. (Box 1)
  - ACME Markets and Teamsters (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Chain (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Associated Grocers & Teamsters (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Baltimore County Board Education / TABCO Feb 13, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Baltimore County Board Education / TABCO Feb 13, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Baltimore County Board Education / TABCO Oct 30 1978 Tabco Bulletin (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Baltimore County Board Education / TABCO (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Baltimore County Board Education / TABCO 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Baltimore County Board Education / TABCO (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Baltimore County Board Education / TABCO Sept 25, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Baltimore County Board Education / TABCO (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Berlin, CT Board of Education & BEA AAA/Hartford (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Boston School Committe & teachers (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Boston School Committee & BTU (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Cambridge Water Works & SEIU 254 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Cape Cod Hospital & Local 880 AAA/Boston (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Coca Cola & Teamster 122 AAA/Boston (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Commonwealth of Massachuesetts & SEIU 509 Dec 5 1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts & AFSCME 1978 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Combustion Engineers & IBB 558 AAA/Hartford (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts & AFSCME Sept 25, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Chester VT (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts & Massachusetts Nurses 1978 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Commonwealth of Mass (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Commonwealth of Mass. - Golnick Aften. (Box 2)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts & AFSCME (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts & Massachusetts Nurses Mediation May 1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts & MNA (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts & SEIU 509 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Concord, Mass (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Conrail 10 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Cranston Schools AAA/Boston (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Fall Mountain (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Fall Mountain Regional High School AAA/Boston (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Falmouth Schools AAA/Boston (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Falmouth Credit Evaluation (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Falmouth School AAA/Boston (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Filene's & Retail Employees 1445 AAA/Boston (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - First National & Retail Clerks AAA/Boston (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Fleet Service & Teamsters 559 AAA/Hartford (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - First National & Meatcutters #2 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - General Dynamics & Shipbuilders #5 Jan 18, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - General Dynamics & Shipbuilders Nov 29, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Gilbert & Bennett & USW 6381 AAA/Hartford (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Gilford Schools, NH AAA/Boston (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Goffstown Schools AAA/Boston (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Golnick Manufacturing & AFTRA (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Greyhound-Foley - Norwalk State College Federation Of Teachers. (Box 3)
  - Greyhound March 28, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Hamden Schools AAA/Hartford #1239-0327-78 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Handy & Harmon & Steelworkers AAA/HART #1230-0414-77 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Hershey & local 464, B&CW (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Hershey Foods Corp. & Chocolate Workers: Second Shift Showering (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Homer D Bronson Company & USW #5104 AAA/Hartford 1230-0419-78 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Homer D Bronson Company & USS AAA/Hartford 1230-0140-78 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Hume Pipe & Steelworkers (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Interstate container & UPIU 1772 AAA/Boston #1130-0715-78 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Hyannis Fire Department AAA/Boston #1139-1509-78 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Kent County and MSTA (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Kent County, Maryland (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Knights of Columbus (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Laconia Needle & USW 171 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Laconia Needle QC Lab Tech (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Magnetic Metals & IUEW 134 AAA/Philadelphia #1430-0805-79S (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Market forge & USW AAA/Boston #1130-1763-78 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Marine Colloids & Cement #411 AAA/Boston #1130-1014-78 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Mass Transit & Transit Union 1300 AAA/Philadelphia 1430-1529-78S (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Middlesex County & AFSCME AAA/Boston 1139-0711-73 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Mobil Oil & IOWU AAA/Phildelphia #1430-1128-78M/J (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Mobil Oil & IOWU AAA/Philadlephia 1430-0443-78M/J (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - National Airlines & IAMAW CASE # MIA-58-76 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Concord, New Hampshire Factfinding April 12, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - New Haven Board of Education & Teachers AAA/Hartford 1239-0317-79 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - New Hampshire Jan 24-26, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Norwalk State College & Federation of Technical College Teachers AAA/Hartford 1239-0002-78 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Northwest IAM Seattle - Pennsyvania Power & Light. (Box 4)
  - Northwest & IAM/Seattle Parking Lot Oct 4, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Northwest & IAM Docket 79-90 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Northwest & BRAC (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Northwest Airlines IBT Sept 26, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Northwest Machinists June 30, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Northwest & BRAC Jan 31, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Northwest (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Northwest & Teamsters Feb 13-14, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Northwest Airlines IAM Sept 27, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Northwest Airlines IBT (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Northwest & Teamster 1 of 3, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Northwest Airlines BRAC Jan 31, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Northwest Airlines BRAC Jan 31, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Northwest Oct 5, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Northwest & BRAC March 7-8, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - NWA and IAM Conveyor (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - NWA and IAM - Case (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Penn Electric & Utility Workers (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - PA Power & Light & IBEW #1600 AAA/Philadelphia (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Philadelphia School Dist. - United Airlines. (Box 5)
  - Philadelphia School District & EMPL 1201 AAA/PHIL 1430-0077-79 M/Q (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Pinkham Lumber & UPIU #1310 AAA/Boston#1130-1212-79 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Proctor & Gamble & IOCW (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Providence Schools & Teachers AAA/Boston #1139-2166-78 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Providence Schools AAA/Boston #1139-0122-79 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Purolator Security & Armored Car AAA/Philadelphia 1430-0892078Q (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Randolph Schools (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - State of Rhode Island & IFPTE AAA/Boston #1139-1300-79 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Rhode Island Department of Education & AFSCME #2872 AAA/Boston #1139-0183-78 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Rock of Ages & Steelworkers (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Salem & AFSCME #1818 AAA/Boston #1130-0795-79 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Slater Dye & ACTWU AAA/Boston #1130-1291-78 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - St. Regis Paper & UPIU #261 AAA/Boston #1130-0778-78 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Stylex and United Bedding Local AAA/Philadelphia (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Teledyne-McKay & Steelworkers AAA/Philadelphia #1430-1711-78 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Thames Valley & American Federation of Teachers #1942 AAA/Hartford 1239-0003-78 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Thompson Steel & USW AAA/Boston #1130-1439-78 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Triangle 7 local 255 AAA/Hartford #1230-0278-79 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - United Airlines & ALPA Case Chi 64-12-2-043-76 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - United Airlines & Flight Attendants March 1978 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - United Airlines & Flight Attendants Aug 21, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - University of Connecticut & AAUP AAA/Hartford #1239-0417-77 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - United airlines June 21, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- United Airlines - United States Post Office. (Box 6)
  - united Airlines & Flight Attendants (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - USPS & NALC Oct 11, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - USPS & APWU March 20, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - USPS & APWU March 13, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - USPS and Letter Carriers (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Local 300, Arbitrations (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - USPO & Mailhandlers Dec 1, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - USPO & Mailhandlers Jan 1, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - USPO and NALC May 14, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - USPO & APWU Dec 5, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - USPS (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - USPS & APWU Sept 13, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- United States Post Office. (Box 7)
  - USPS & APWU (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - USPS & APWU 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - USPS & APWU 3 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - USPS & Mailhandlers Jan 29, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - USPS & P.O. Mailhandlers Oct 26, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - USPS & APWU Sept 14, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - USPS & Mailhandlers March 19, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - USPS Mailhandler (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - USPS & APWU June 5, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- United States Post Office - Yale University. (Box 8)
  - USPS v DeVivo (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - USPS - NYC (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - USPS & APWU Nov 19, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - USPS & APWU (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - USPS & APWU Jan 6, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - USPS & APWU Removal (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - USPS & NALC March 15, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - USPS & APWU March 16, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - USPS & NALC March 13, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - USPS & APWU April 11, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - USPS & APWU April 10, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - USPS & NALC May 8, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - USPS & APWU April 13, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - USPO & APWU April 14, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - USPS & APWU July 25, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - USPS & APWU (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - USPS & APWU May 16, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - USPS & APWU (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - USPS & APWU May 25, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - USPS & NALC June 6, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Warwick School Comm & Teachers AAA/Boston (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Yale University & Federation of University Employees #35 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Yale University & Federation of University Employees #35 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - USPS & APWU Nov 20, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Woonsocket Schools and Teachers (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Woonsocket Schools & teachers AAA/Boston (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Winsted Hospital & Health Assoc AAA/Hartford (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - USPS & NALC Feb 6, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - USPS & APWU Jan 16, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - USPS & APWU Jan 16, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - USPS & NALC Sept 6, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - USPS & NALC Sept 6, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - USPS & NALC Sept 6, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 30)